travelspot.us 2011-01-06

# TravelSpot

### TravelSpot.US is strongly committed to protecting your privacy

TravelSpot.US is a division of One Travel and this privacy statement covers the site TravelSpot.US. TravelSpot.US is fully committed to providing the highest standard of privacy for personal information.

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information only for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

We do not sell, trade, share or rent your personal information to others, without your prior consent. We keep your personal information private and secure, in our databases and during transfer to our third party marketing partners. When you use our system, you are asked to provide your name, email address and other information. We use this information to answer your questions and process your requests for services from us and/or for products or services from our third party marketing partners.

In order to keep you informed about our latest services, we may notify you via email newsletter of any changes or new additions to our site. You may unsubscribe from our email newsletter by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email you receive from us.

Other sites accessible through our web site have their own privacy policies and data collection practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. TravelSpot.US is not responsible for the actions of third parties.

This web site uses cookies to personalize your experience at this site, and optionally to speed up the member sign in process. Cookies are information stored on your computer. Cookies are not used to track your movement or perform any function other than to enhance your use of this site. If your browser does not support cookies, or you have not enabled cookies on your browser, many of these time-saving features will not work properly. Also, you need to have cookies enabled in your browser if you want to enter the member's area. Some of our business partners (Traffic Analyzing Software) use cookies on our site. We have no access to, or, control over such cookies.

We use an outside shipping company to ship paper tickets, and a credit card processing company to bill you for travel products. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [TravelSpot.US](http://www.travelspot.us/) only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://www.verisign.com/ssl/ssl-information-center/how-ssl-security-works/index.html>.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [AffiliateSupport@TravelSpot.US](mailto:affiliatesupport@travelspot.us).

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

### CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement page, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage

### ACCESS TO PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Should your personally identifiable information change, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at [AffiliateSupport@TravelSpot.US](mailto:affiliatesupport@travelspot.us) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a travel product but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by contacting us at the address below.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

Should you have questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at:

TravelSpot.US  
One Travel  
1050 East Flamingo Road  
Suite S-302  
Las Vegas, NV 89119
